Thank you guys for having us over.
谢谢你们准备了这一切.
-Yeah, this is fun, couples night. -I don't know why we don't hang out..
-这是为可爱的夫妻准备的. -我不知道
-with married couples more often. -Because every time we do..
-为什么我们不多来几次这样的聚会. -也许是因为每次我们吃饭..
you make jokes about swinging and scare them away.
你总是开玩笑, 把他们吓跑了.
You mean that Portuguese couple? Yeah, like you wouldn't have done it.
你是指那对葡萄牙人?  好象你没有做过一样.
Hey, you guys, I have great news.
嗨, 各位, 我有个好消息.
-We're kind of in the middle of dinner. -Oh, well, I already ate, but sure.
-罗斯. 我们似乎还在吃饭. -呃..我已经吃过了, 不过...好吧.
Guess what happened at work today.
猜猜今天工作上发生了什么?
A dinosaur died a million years ago?
一只恐龙在一百万年前死了?
Try 65 million years ago. And then try:
应该是6千5百万年前 请闭嘴~~
My tenure review board met today, and I hear it's looking really good.
我的工作续约考察会议今天开了 我听说进展得不错.
Yeah, do you have any idea what this means in academic circles?
你知道这在学院圈子里意味着什么吗,
I am gonna get laid.
我可以留下来了.
-Hi, you guys. -Hey.
-嘿, 大伙. -嘿
Oh, Italian.
意大利风味～
No one.. No one wanted seconds, right?
还有人好说话吗?
No, I'm good.
不, 不, 我很好.
Guys, you're never gonna believe it. This headhunter called me.
嘿, 你们一定不相信? 猎头给我打了电话
I have a meeting tomorrow with Gucci. Gucci wants me.
说Gucci(品牌)要和我面试. Gucci会聘用我!
-I'm up for tenure. -Congratulations.
-我可以续约了. -祝贺你.
You too. What are the odds?
你也是. 真巧!
Guess what?
猜发生了什么?
I finally got that seed out of my teeth.
我终于把那个核从我的牙齿里弄出来了.
I don't know who I'm happiest for.
我真不知道我最该为谁感到高兴?
I do. He's been working on that all day.
我知道. 他一整天都在弄它!
The One with Princess Consuela
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Hey, Mon, was it weird changing your name to Geller Bing?
嘿, 莫妮卡, 把你的名字改成盖勒.宾奇怪吗?
No. No, it felt nice to acknowledge this.
不, 不. 承认这样也挺好.
-Where'd you go to do it? -The..
-你打算在哪里办? -呃..
The Ministry of Names..
姓名...服务
Bureau.
事务所..
You never did it.
你没有改过!
I'm sorry. It's just the idea of..
我很抱歉. 变成正式的
Of being an official Bing.
宾的想法…….
Hey, I will have you know that..
嘿! 我得让你知道..啊..
Who am I kidding? Let's call the kid Geller and let Bing die with me.
我真是在开玩笑. 就让孩子叫 盖勒 让 宾 随着我到死.
-Here you go. -Thanks.
-给你 -谢谢
Honey, would you want me to take your name?
亲爱的, 你想要我随你的名字吗?
Oh, it's up to you. It's your name. You've gotta live with it.
你决定吧. 这是你的名字. 你有特权.
-Let's see. Call me Mrs. Hannigan. -Mrs. Hannigan?
-让我想想. 叫我哈得根夫人. -哈得根 夫人?
Can't you see I'm in the middle of something?
什么? 你不觉得我的名字在什么东西的当中吗?
I like it.
我喜欢.
-Hey, guys. -Hey, Joe.
-嘿, 大伙! -嘿, 乔伊
We got things to check out at the new house. You want to come?
我们还有些事要做, 我们要去看新房子. 你想和我们一起去吗?
-No, thank you. -You're not happy about us moving..
-不, 谢了. -我们搬家你不高兴了
but you're the only one who hasn't seen the house.
但你是唯一没有看过我们新房子的人.
Yeah, come with us. You'll see how close it is.
是啊. 和我们一起去吧, 你会知道那离城很近.
No, it's not close. You said it was in escrow.
不, 才不近. 你说它在'契约'里.
I couldn't even find that on the map.
我在地图上都找不到那地方.
No, Joey. Escrow is..
不, 乔伊. 契约是..
There's money, and..
这有钱, 而且...
It's not the bank exactly.
却不是银行
I don't know what it is.
我不知道它是什么
Joey, please come. It would mean so much to us.
乔伊, 求你来吧. 你对我们真的很重要.
You know what? You are my friends. I want to be supportive.
知道吗, 你是我们的朋友. 我需要支持.
I will come with you. Shotgun.
我会和你们一起去的, 决定了！
Damn it.
太好了.
See you guys later. We'll pick you up at 11.
一会见. 我们11点接你.
-So glad you're coming. -All right.
-真高兴你能来. -好
-Good for you. That was really mature. -What? The only reason I'm going..
-真不错. 你够成熟了. -什么? 不. 我去那所破房子唯一的原因是
to their stupid house is to point out everything wrong with it..
我能说出里面所有的缺点
so they don't move. I'm gonna make them stay here.
让他们不要住进去. 我要他们留在这里.
You're a strange kind of grownup.
你的力气长了不少.
Joey, you can't make someone do something they don't want to do.
乔伊, 你不能让别人做他们不愿做的事.
Believe me. There's something I've been trying to get Mike to do in bed, and..
相信我, 有些事我想让麦克在床上做 但他....
-Can we not talk about that now? -All right. Prude.
-我们现在不谈那个. -好吧, 假正经
Look, Monica and Chandler really love this house.
听着. 莫妮卡和钱德真的很喜欢那所房子.
You are not gonna talk them into staying here.
你不应该说服他们住在这里
Hey, I can convince people to do anything, you know?
嘿, 我能说服人们做任何事情
I bet I could even get Mike to do that thing. What is it?
我打赌我能让麦克做那事. 那是什么?
I am not gonna help you do that!
我才不要帮你做那个!
Oh, my God.
哦, 我的天
Hi. I'm here to see Mr. Campbell, with Gucci.
嗨, 我来见Gucci的坎贝尔先生
The reservation's probably under Gucci.
这个位子也许就是Gucci预定的.
It's spelled like "gucky, " which can be confusing.
拼起来像"拜火教徒"(Gukki), 也许会弄错!
Mr. Campbell's not here yet. Let me show you to his table.
坎贝尔现在还没到. 我带你到他的位子.
Oh, my God. That's my boss. You have to seat us somewhere else.
哦, 我的天. 那是我的老板. 你必须把位子安排在别处.
I'm sorry, that's always Mr. Campbell's table.
我很抱歉. 这一直是坎贝尔先生的桌子.
But my boss cannot see me. I'm interviewing for another job.
但我的老板不能在这看到我. 我在面试另一个工作.
I know. With "gucky."
我知道, 面试"拜火教徒"(Gukki).
-Rachel? -I'm on a date.
-瑞秋 -我在约会
That's great.
太好了.
Yeah, it is. Yeah, you know, it's tough. Single mom. Career.
是啊. 这是艰苦的男人的工作.
You gotta get out there.
你必须离开这里.
Well, you've got a good energy.
呃, 你很有精力.
-Rachel? -Yes, hi.
-瑞秋?  -是的
-James Campbell. -Hi.
-詹姆斯.坎贝尔 -嗨
-Excuse us. -Please.
-抱歉. -请坐
He's cute.
他很可爱.
Thank you, JewHunks.com, huh?
谢谢, JewHunks.com, 哈?
So..
所以.
your resume is quite impressive.
你的简历很好.
My resume?
我的简历..
I wouldn't.. I wouldn't call my online dating profile a resume.
我不会把我的私人约会文件称做简历.
Dating profile? No, I'm.. I'm talking about the work resume.
约会简历?不, 我是说..我是说工作简历
Whatever happened to just singing for no reason?
不论发生什么, 就只是毫无理由得唱歌.
Maybe people found it weird.
也许别人觉得奇怪.
So..
也许
-Why do you want to leave Ralph Lauren? -What?
-你为什么想离开拉夫.劳伦? -什么?
-I don't. -You don't?
-我, 我没有. -你没有?
No, I love.. I love it there.
不. 我喜欢那里.
Well, if you don't want to leave, why are we having this lunch?
如果你不想离开, 为什么我们在这里吃午饭呢?
What?
什么?
That's Hugo Boss?
那是Hugo Boss(著名品牌)?
I believe what she's trying to tell you is that I'm her boss.
我觉得她想告诉你的是我是她老板
Mr. Boss..
Boss先生.
it is a pleasure to meet you.
见到你很高兴
This place is so depressing. If I had to work here, I'd kill myself.
这个地方太令人伤心了.  如果我在这里工作, 我会自杀的.
But you obviously haven't.
显然你不在.
-How can I help you? -I need to change my name, please.
-我能帮你吗? -我想要改我的名字.
See, I need to change it because I'm hiding from the law.
我想改掉它因为我在逃避法律.
You're fun.
你很好.
-You need to fill out this form. -Okay. Well, just so I know..
-请填一下这个表格. -好
I don't know how it works. My name is Buffay..
我只是不知道应该怎么做, 看, 我叫布费
and my husband's name is Hannigan.
我丈夫叫哈得根
So is it supposed to be "Buffay-Hannigan" or "Hannigan-Buffay"?
那么应该是布费.哈得根 还是哈得根.布费?
-It can be anything you want. -Well, not anything.
-你想什么就是什么 -任何名字? .
Yeah. Anything.
是..任何
Oh, this could take a while.
哦, 那需要花些时间.
-Get out of my line. -Okay.
-站到一边去. -好
-Hey. -Hey, Phoebe.
-嘿 -嘿, 菲比
Oh, not anymore. I changed it today.
不再是了. 我今天改了我的名字.
-Oh, I'm sorry, Mrs. Hannigan. -Wrong again.
-抱歉.  哈得根夫人. -又错了.
Apparently, you can change it to anything.
显然你能改成任何你想要的名字
So I thought, "All right, here's an opportunity to be creative."
所以我想, 这是发挥想象力的好机会.
So meet Princess Consuela Bananahammock.
所以来见过康斯薇拉.巴娜娜.哈莫克公主.
That's what we were gonna name the baby.
那是我想给我们宝宝的名字.
-Phoebe. -Princess Consuela.
-菲比 -康斯薇拉公主.
You seriously changed your name to that?
你真的把你的名字改成那个了?
Okay, so from now on, we have to call you Princess Consuela?
好吧. 从今往后我们得叫你康斯薇拉公主了?
No, I'm gonna have my friends call me Valerie.
我知道. 我想让我的朋友叫我瓦莱丽.
-Hey, how did the interview go? -Not good.
-嘿, 面试如何? -不妙.
I always feel that way after an interview. I'll bet it went better than you think.
你知道吗, 我经常这么觉得. 我打赌那会比你想得好.
Well, I didn't get the job at Gucci and I got fired from Ralph Lauren.
哎, 我没有得到Gucci的工作, 还丢了拉夫.劳伦的工作.
That is a bad interview.
那面试的确不好.
What are you talking about? How did this happen?
你在说什么呀? 怎么会这样?
My boss was at the same restaurant where I was having my interview..
我老板在同一家餐厅 我在那里面试...
and he heard everything.
他听见了一切.
Later, he calls me into his office and tells me he'll have to let me go..
后来他把我叫到他的办公室, 告诉我他要解雇我
because I'm not a team player.
因为我不合群.
And I said, "Wait a minute. Yes, I am."
然后我说“等等, 恩, 我的确不合群”
And then I had to sit there for 45 minutes..
然后我得在那里坐45分钟
while he proved that that, in fact, was true.
而他证明了, 事实是这样的.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
哦, 真抱歉.
Hey.
嘿
What..? What's this?
这, 这是什么?
Why, it's a bottle of champagne. Why is this here?
是一瓶香槟! 为了什么?
-Ross. -I guess it's here..
-罗斯 -我想是
because I got tenure!
因为我得到了续约!
-Congratulations. -Congratulations.
-恭喜你. -恭喜你.
This is the single greatest day of my professional career.
这是我职业生涯中最伟大的一天.
-Gunther. Six glasses. -Six?
-冈瑟, 6个杯子. -6个?
-You want me to join you? -I thought Joey was here. Five is good.
-你要我也喝? -我以为乔伊也在这儿 5个好了
Wow, I'm gonna have a loogey in my coffee tomorrow.
明天我要小心我的咖啡了..
-Okay, I'll tell him. -No. No, nobody tell him.
-好吧, 我告诉他 -不不, 谁也别告诉他
This is a big night for him. I don't wanna spoil it.
今晚对他很重要, 我不想破坏它
-Are you sure? -Yeah. I'll be fine.
-你确定? -对, 确定
Okay. Everybody take one, okay?
好吧. 大家都来一杯怎样?
Israeli champagne.
以色列香槟
And it's vanilla.
还是香草味的
I got tenure. I didn't win the lottery.
我有了续约, 但我没有赢彩票.
Hey, Rach, so how did your thing go?
嘿, 瑞秋, 你的事怎么了?
Good. But I won't hear about that for a couple days.
挺好, 但是要几天以后再出结果.
Oh, you know what, you're gonna get it. I can feel it.
你知道吗, 你会得到工作的. 我能感觉到.
Can you?
你能吗?
All right, everybody, here's to Ross.
好的, 为了罗斯
And to years of hard work finally paying off.
为了几年的艰苦工作终于有了回报.
And to knowing that your career doesn't mean everything.
为了懂得你的工作并不意味着什么.
But also knowing it means a lot.
也为了懂得它意味着很多.
But more importantly, to full, well-rounded lives.
更为了多彩丰富的生活.
That center around work.
以工作为中心.
-To Ross. -To Ross.
-为了罗斯 -为了罗斯
You know what the best part about this is? I can never be fired.
你知道最棒的是什么吗? 我永远都不会失业.
-Oh, God. -No, seriously.
-哦, 天啊 -不, 说正经的.
I have job security for life.
我有了终生工作保障
You know? I mean, I never have to worry.
我是说我永远都不必为它而担心了.
Oh, look at you. Look how happy you are for me.
看看你. 看你多为我高兴.
No, it's not that. I got fired today.
不, 不是那样, 我今天被辞退了
And I didn't get the other job.
而且又没有得到新的工作.
Rach, I'm so sorry.
瑞秋, 很抱歉
-Great, I feel like an idiot. -No, it's okay. You didn't know.
-太好了. 我觉得像个白痴. -不, 没什么. 你不知道.
Little heads-up would've been nice.
小小的机智应该会很好.
Thank you for letting us see the house again.
谢谢你再让他看看房子.
And thank you for explaining to us what escrow means.
也谢谢你解释 '契约'...
I've already forgotten what you said, but thank you.
我已经忘了你说什么. 但是, 谢谢你.
Take as long as you want. Just let me know when you're through.
想待多久就待多久. 你们看完之后告诉我.
-So glad you decided to come. -Me too. Yeah, this place is great.
-很高兴你决定来. -我也是. 这地方真好.
So happy for you guys. Although, you know, I hope you like fungus.
真为你们高兴. 尽管你们知道我希望你们像蘑菇一样.
-What? -Fungus.
-什么? -蘑菇.
Yeah. Place is full of it.
它们在任何地方都有.
No, it's not. We had an inspection and they didn't find anything.
不, 才不是. 我们检查过但没有找到不对的地方.
Okay. Then I guess I have dry eyes and a scratchy throat for no reason.
好吧. 我想我毫无原因地眼睛干燥喉咙痛.
Maybe it's because you hung your head out the window like a dog..
也许是因为你整夜把头伸在窗外的缘故.
the whole ride here.
路上都伸在外面
Maybe.
也许.
So this is the living room, huh? It's pretty dark.
那这是客厅? 哦, 真暗啊.
-No, it's not. -Are you kidding?
-才不是. -你在开玩笑.
I think I just saw a bat in the corner.
我想我刚才在角落看到只蝙蝠.
When your head was hanging out the window, it didn't hit a mailbox, did it?
当你的头伸在窗外的时候?  没有撞到信箱吧?
Maybe.
也许.
Look, I just think you guys can do better than this house, you know?
我只是觉得你们不买这个房子更好些,
Or any other house for that matter.
或者另一所房子.
Oh, Joey.
哦, 乔伊
We know you're having a hard time with this, but we..
我们知道你觉得不好受, 但我们..
-We love it here. -Fine! If you love this house so much..
-真的喜欢这里. -好吧. 好吧. 如果你喜欢这所房子
you should live here. Okay? I hope you get used to that weird humming sound.
你就应该住在这里? 我只是希望你们能习惯那种奇怪的声音.
-Joey, we know that's you. -No..
-乔伊, 我们知道那是你. -不..
it's not.
不是的.
-Welcome back. -I missed you.
-欢迎回来. -我想你.
-Oh, me too. -So, what's new?
-哦, 我也是. -有什么新鲜事?
Well, I am no longer Phoebe Buffay.
我不再是菲比.布费
-That's great. You changed your name? -Yes, I did.
-太棒了. 你改名字了? -是的.
Meet Princess Consuela Bananahammock.
康斯薇拉.巴娜娜.哈莫克公主.
-You're kidding, right? -Nope.
-你在开玩笑? -不.
-You really did that? -Yep.
-你真的那么做了? -对.
You can't do that.
你不能那么做.
Why?
为什么?
Why? It's fun. It's different. No one else has a name like it.
为什么? 那很好玩 . 很不同. 没有人有那样的名字
Then I'm gonna change my name.
好吧. 我也要改我的名字.
Great. Okay, what are you gonna change it to?
好. 你要改成什么?
Crap Bag.
废物.
-Mike Crap Bag? -No. No "Mike." No, just "Crap Bag."
-麦克废物? -不. 没有麦克. 不. 仅仅是废物.
First name: Crap. Last name: Bag.
姓废 名物.
-You're not serious, right? -Yeah, I'm serious.
-你不是认真的吧? -我是认真的.
It's fun, it's different, and no one else has a name like that.
很好玩. 那很不同. 没有人用这样的名字.
Well, then great. If you love it, I love it.
好吧. 如果你喜欢, 我就喜欢.
I do love it. And I love your name. I love Princess Consuela.
我的确喜欢. 我也喜欢你的名字. 我喜欢康斯薇拉公主.
And I love Crap.
我喜欢废物.
-Who are you? -Oh, hi. I'm Joey.
-你是谁? -哦, 是乔伊
My stupid friends are buying this house. Who are you?
我愚蠢的朋友要买这所房子, 你是谁?
I'm Mackenzie. My stupid parents are selling this house.
我是麦坎西. 我愚蠢的父母要卖这所房子.
I hate my parents.
我恨我的父母.
I hate my friends.
我恨我的朋友.
Look, there's gotta be a way that we can stop this from happening.
瞧, 我们能做一些事阻止他们.
Like what?
比如?
Okay, you come with me and you tell them that the house is haunted.
你跟我来告诉他们这房子闹鬼.
What are you,8?
你才8岁吗?
-Okay. Let's hear your great idea. -I don't have any great ideas.
-好吧, 你有什么好主意. -我没有好主意
I am 8.
我才8岁.
There's gotta be a way. I mean, you know..
一定要想一个办法.
if Monica and Chandler move here, and Phoebe's married to Mike..
我是说, 你知道, 莫妮卡和钱德搬走了 菲比和麦克结婚了.
that just leaves me and Ross and Rach. You know what I mean?
只剩我和罗斯和瑞秋, 你知道意味着什么吗?
I really don't.
不太知道.
What am I gonna do? I feel like I'm losing my friends.
我能作什么? 我觉得我要失去我的朋友了.
-My parents say I'll make new friends. -Yeah, sure, easy for you.
-我父母说我能交到新的朋友. -好吧, 对你而言很容易.
You're young. Me? I'm set in my ways.
你比我年轻. 我只能自己伤心.
This is what my mom was talking about. Whiners are wieners.
那就是我妈妈一直说的: 哭哭啼啼的人始终哭哭啼啼.
Look, you want your friends to be happy, right?
好吧. 你希望你的朋友开心, 是吗?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. Yeah.
是的. 我想是的.
Well, if moving here is gonna make them happy, don't you want them to do it?
搬到这里来会让他们开心的. 你难道不希望他们这样吗?
Yeah. Maybe.
也许.
Then you've gotta let them go.
那你就应该让他们走.
Oh, I hate to admit it, but you're..
我恨承认这个, 但你也许..
You're probably right.
是对的.
How'd you get to be so smart?
你怎么那么会说话?
I read a lot.
我读了很多书.
Just when I thought we could be friends.
我认为我们能成为朋友.
Oh, hey, Rach. I just heard. I'm so sorry.
这里, 瑞秋. 我刚听见. 我很抱歉.
Oh, thank you..
哦, 谢谢.
You still don't know my name, do you?
还是不知道我的名字, 是吗?
Well, now I don't have to.
现在我不用知道了.
Ross, what is taking you so long?
罗斯, 你怎么那么慢?
I'm sorry. It's almost as if this wasn't built for a quick getaway.
抱歉.我得说它的尺寸不适合搬动.
Rachel?
瑞秋?
Mark? Oh, my God.
马克? 哦, 天
-How have you been? -Fantastic. You remember Ross.
-你怎么样? -太好了! 你记得罗斯?
Sure. Sure.
当然.
What's with the chair?
椅子怎么了?
You know, you can't always get a seat on the subway, so..
你知道, 在地铁上没有座位...
Clever.
真聪明.
So how are you?
你怎么样?
You're not catching me on my best day.
真不巧.
Yeah, a box full of your desk stuff doesn't say "big promotion."
你办公桌里的东西不太安稳
No, but it's good. You know, I'm gonna take some time off..
不, 但那很好, 你知道. 我要休息一段时间..
-and do charity work. -Are you sure?
-做一些慈善工作. -你肯定?
We may have something at Louis Vuitton.
我想我们现在需要人手.
Screw charity work. What do you got?
慈善工作, 你们有什么?
Why don't we have dinner and talk?
我们边吃饭边讨论吧?
-Great. I'll call you. -Okay.
-我给你打电话. -好吧
-Nice to see you again. -Yeah. Yeah. I got tenure.
-很高兴见到你. -啊..我有持续工作.
Oh, my God.
哦, 我的天.
See? I told you something good would come along.
看到没有, 我告诉你好事会来的.
And he seemed really nice. I've met him before?
他看起来真不错.我以前见过他吗?
Ross, that's Mark.
罗斯, 那是马克.
From Bloomingdale's? You were insanely jealous of him.
Bloomingdales, 你嫉妒得发狂.
-That is Mark? -Yes.
-那是马克  -是啊
I hate that guy.
我恨他.
No, no, no. You cannot go to dinner with him.
不, 不. 你不能和他吃饭.
-What? You don't want me to get a job? -Yeah, I'm sure he'll give you a job.
-什么? 你不希望我有这份工作? -当然. 我肯定他会给你一份工作.
Maybe make you his "sex-cretary."
也许让你当他的性伴侣.
I'm serious. I just don't trust that guy, okay?
我是认真的. 我只是不相信他
You know what..? Okay, let's talk about it later. There comes security.
罗斯, 你知道吗? 好, 我们以后再谈. 保安来了.
Oh, I love this street.
我喜欢这个街道.
The trees and the big front yards and the actual picket fences.
树, 大的前院. 那个树桩.
Man, those two dogs are going at it.
那是两只狗!
-Hey. Where you been? -Oh, just, you know, looking around.
-嘿. 你到哪里去了? -哦, 只是随处走走.
But you know what?
你知道吗
This house is great.
这房子太棒了.
Really? What changed your mind?
真的, 什么使你改变了?
The little girl who lives here made me feel better about the whole thing.
那个住在这里的小姑娘让我觉得好点.
Joey? There was a little girl who lived here, but she died, like, 30 years ago.
乔伊, 以前有小姑娘住在这儿但30年前就死了.
What?
什么?
I'm just messing with you.
我只是在吓你.
That's not funny. You know I'm afraid of little-girl ghosts.
这不好笑. 你知道我害怕小鬼.
Now that you're okay with the house, do you want to go see your room?
现在你喜欢这房子了, 你想看看你的房间吗?
What?
什么?
I get my own room?
我会有我自己的房间?
You don't think we'd buy a house and not have a Joey room, do you?
你不会认为我们买了房子却没有给你房间吧?
Oh, my God.
噢, 天.
Hey, can I have an aquarium? And a sex swing?
我能有个鱼缸吗? 加个做爱秋千?
-No. -Why not? I'll keep the tank clean.
-不. -为什么不行? 我会保持干净的.
After you, Ms. Bananahammock.
你先请, 巴娜娜.哈莫克夫人.
Thank you, Mr. Bag.
谢谢,  废先生.
-Oh, hi, Rita. -How are you?
-哦, 你好 瑞塔. -你怎么样?
Good. Oh, Rita's a massage client.
瑞塔是一个按摩的客户.
Yeah.
哦
Why don't you introduce me?
你为什么不介绍我?
Rita, this is my husband.
瑞塔, 这是我的丈夫.
Why don't you tell her my name?
我要你告诉她我的名字.
Okay, I will. This is.. This is my husband, Crap Bag.
好的, 我会的 这是我的丈夫废物.
Crap Bag?
废物?
If you need an easy way to remember it, just think of a bag of crap.
如果你需要记得简单点, 就把它想象成一包垃圾.
-Okay. Excuse me. -Yeah.
-好的, 少陪了. -好
Okay, fine, you made your point. Can you please just be Mike Hannigan again?
好吧. 你的目的达到了. 你能再做我的麦克.哈得根?
Only if you'll be Phoebe Buffay.
如果你还是菲比.布费
How about..? How about Buffay-Hannigan?
布费-哈得根怎么样?
Really?
真的?
Yeah. I'm Phoebe Buffay-Hannigan-Bananahammock.
是, 我是菲比.布费-哈得根.巴娜娜.哈莫克
Do you even know what a banana hammock is?
你知道巴娜娜.哈莫克是什么吗?
It's a funny word.
那是个有趣的字.
It's a Speedo.
那是一种速率器.
Oh, crap.
噢, 废物
-What are you thinking about? -Oh, you know.
-你在想什么 -哦…
The two dogs.
那两只狗
-Hey, is Rachel here? -Nope.
-嘿, 瑞秋在吗?  -不.
She's still at dinner?
她还在吃晚饭?
-I guess. Why, who's she with? -That guy, Mark..
-我想是的. 她和谁在一起? -是马克.
from Bloomingdale's. She thinks he's just being nice to her.
一个家伙从 Bloomingdales来. 她认为他只是对她好,
But I know he really wants to sleep with her.
但我知道他想和她睡.
It's seven years ago.
已经7年了.
My time machine works.
我的时间机器起作用了!
We ran into him on the street today, and he said he might have a job for her.
我们今天在路上碰到他 他说也许他有工作给她
But I know he just wants to get into her pants.
但我知道他只是想让她接近他的裤子.
So, what if he wants to sleep with her? I mean, she's single, and he's cute.
那为什么他不想和她睡?  我是说她单身而且漂亮.
Excuse me?
什么?
Oh, please.
哦, 拜托
Yesterday, on the subway, you couldn't stop staring..
昨天在地铁上, 你不停地..
at that woman with the big breasts.
盯着一个大胸脯的女人看
For your information, I was staring at her baby.
象你看到的那样, 我在看她的宝宝.
We're about to be parents.
我们就要做父母了.
Oh, sorry.
哦, 对不起
-Hi, you guys. -Hi. So..
-嗨  大伙. -嗨.
-how was dinner? -Oh, it was great. Mark is so sweet.
-晚饭怎么样? -噢, 很棒. Mark很好.
Oh, yeah? Yeah, I wonder why? What could that smarmy letch possibly want?
哦, 是吗, 我想知道为什么. 那个聪明的人更可能需要什么?
Oh, Ross. Come on. He is happily married. His wife just had twins.
哦, 罗斯, 别这样 他已经结婚了, 他的妻子生了双胞胎.
Should we send something?
我们说什么了?
How did the job stuff go?
工作怎么样?
He offered me one.
他给了我一个.
-That's great. -Congratulations.
-太棒了! -恭喜你
I know, it's amazing.
我知道那很棒.
It's amazing. It's so much better than what I had at Ralph Lauren.
那很棒. 比我在拉夫.劳伦要好得多.
-The money is great. -Can we..?
-薪水很不错. -我们?
Can we just stop for a second? Who said something better would come along?
我们能停一停吗. 是谁说一切都会好起来的, 啊?
You didn't believe me. I told you everything was gonna work out.
你不相信我. 我告诉你一切都会有起色.
You know what? This calls for a bottle of Israel's finest.
你知道吗, 这时候该来一瓶以色列佳酿
The job is in Paris.
工作在巴黎.
I mean, this soap opera is a great gig..
我是说, 肥皂剧是很好的机会...
but am I missing opportunities?
但, 我错过了机会吗?
You know, I've always thought of myself as a serious actor.
你知道, 我总是觉得我自己是个严肃的演员.
Should I be trying to do more independent movies?
我指, 我是不是应该尝试更多的独立电影?
I don't know.
我不知道.
But you know what? I'm gonna put you on with my bear.
你知道吗, 我让我的熊听电话.
Hold on.
等等.
Hey, Bailey, I need some career advice.
嘿, 小熊, 我需要一些事业上的意见.